Guide to the Dan Miller Photographs Collection PHOTOS.120
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Unions.
  - Subseries I:L: Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers Union.
    - "Jam Juniors Button" [Total negs: 12], Jun 29, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11766)
    - Membership Meeting Goldberg Goodal Statler Hilton [Total negs: 24], Oct 21, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11767)
    - Morse Electro Co. Flm at work [Total negs: 72], Nov 27, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11768)
    - Photo Stories [?] "Bochroth" and "Resina" [?] [Total negs: 80], Dec 21, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11769)
    - Morse Contract Meeting [Total negs: 54], May 24, 1905 (Box 13, Item 11784)
    - Memorial Dr. Martin Luther King 149 W. 28th St. [Total negs: 52], Jan 15, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11770)
    - Newark, N. J. Quarterly Newark [?] Leather [?] Division Meeting [Total negs: 35], Feb 23, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11771)
    - Membership Meeting 250 W. 26th St. [Total negs: 63], Feb 25, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11772)
    - Trustee Meetings Portraits [Total negs: 110], Feb 26, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11773)
    - Foner (Loraine) Birthday [Total negs: 47], Mar 2, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11774)
    - Check Presentations [Total negs: 7], Mar 2, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11775)
    - Freedom Festival & Dance 310 West 43rd [?] St. [Total negs: 52], Mar 13, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11776)
    - S. S. and Executive Bd. Training Programs Newark, N. J. [Total negs: 36], Mar 30, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11777)
    - D. A. Thomas Mackell [?] Queens Court House [Total negs: 8], Apr 7, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11778)
    - Blood Bank [Total negs: 30], Apr 22, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11779)
    - Copy neg. Tony Barotta [Total negs: 4], May 1971 (Box 13, Item 11780)
    - Contract Signing Harper and Row 49 E. 33rd St. [Total negs: 13], May 6, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11781)
    - Testimonial Dinner "Bernie Woolis [?]" Americana [Total negs: 72], Jun 17, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11782)
    - Morse Dinner Election Lisa Tenod [?] Brooklyn. [Total negs: 78], Jun 24, 1971 (Box 13, Item 11783)
    - Seton [?] N. J. Contract Meeting Retirement Meeting [Total negs: 51], Mar 9, 1972 (Box 13, Item 11785)
    - Jt. Board Local 27 Newark, N. J. [Total negs: 20], Nov 26, 1969 (Box 12, Item 11753)
    - Portrait - Hudson Bay Leola Dunlop [?] -- Neumann Leather [?] Hoboken, N. J. Nomination Meeting and Plant Photos [Total negs: 63], Mar 14, 1972 (Box 13, Item 11786)
    - Jt. Board Blood Bank [Total negs: 25], Apr 25, 1972 (Box 13, Item 11787)
    - Jt. Board Ocean Leather Contract Signing and Morse Bkln Blood Bank [Total negs: 30], May 22, 1972 (Box 13, Item 11788)
    - Installation of Officers Statler Hilton [Total negs: 47], Jun 8, 1972 (Box 13, Item 11789)
    - Retirement Tony Basata [?] [Total negs: 37], Jun 9, 1972 (Box 13, Item 11790)
    - Dyns [?] Jorlson [?] Hts., L. I. Employees at work [?] Campaign Buttons [Total negs: 35], Oct 9, 1972 (Box 13, Item 11791)
    - Portrait Steve Nelson [Total negs: 20], Dec 9, 1974 (Box 13, Item 11792)
    - Steve Nelson Dinner [Total negs: 139], Feb 16, 1975 (Box 13, Item 11793)
    - Jt. Bd. Hudson Bay Union Labels [Total negs: 24], May 28, 1975 (Box 13, Item 11794)
  - Subseries I:M: Glaziers, Local 1087.
    - Opening in Roof Holy Rosary [Total negs: 17], Dec 4, 1968 (Box 14, Item 11816)
    - Kips Bay Boys Club Bronx, N. Y. [Total negs: 11], Jan 17, 1969 (Box 14, Item 11817)
    - Window Photos [Total negs: 14], Oct 20, 1969 (Box 14, Item 11818)
  - Subseries I:N: Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union.
    - Sub-Subseries I:N:1 HERE, Local 6
      - Basketball Teams [Total negs: 19], Jan 5, 1995 (Box 8, Item 11597)
      - Basketball Team and Action Shots [Total negs: 63], Jan 12, 1995 (Box 8, Item 11598)
      - Membership Meeting [Total negs: 48], May 5, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11604)
      - Delegate Meeting [Total negs: 94], May 10, 1995 (Box 8, Item 11599)
      - Hotel Trades Delegate Meeting [Total negs: 18], May 12, 1995 (Box 8, Item 11600)
      - Hotel Trades Delegate Meeting [Total negs: 22], May 15, 1995 (Box 8, Item 11601)
      - Governor Pataki Cocktail Reception, St. Regis Hotel [Total negs: 59], May 24, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11602)
      - Plaza Hotel, Check Presentation Meeting [Total negs: 27], May 25, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11603)
      - Sheraton, Annual Scholarship Awards [Total negs: 136], Jun 8, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11605)
      - ITP Certification [Total negs: 256], Jun 21, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11606)
      - General Delegate Meeting, New York Coliseum [Total negs: 71], Jun 27, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11607)
      - Voting: Plaza Waldorf, Sheraton, Grand Hyatt, New York Hilton, Union Hall [Total negs: 100], Jun 30, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11617)
      - Ratification Meeting [Total negs: 23], Jul 5, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11608)
      - Ratification Meeting [separated from Shoot # 11608] [Total negs: 182], Jul 5, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11618)
      - Randalls Island Picnic & All Star Softball Game [Total negs: 73], Sep 9, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11609)
      - Portrait Delegate Assembly [Total negs: 65], Sep 19, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11610)
      - Contract Ratification Signing-Members-Voting [Total negs: 25], Oct 4, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11611)
      - Demonstration Sen. D'Amato's Office [Total negs: 36], Oct 11, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11612)
      - Hotel Voice ITP Closses [?] [Total negs: 30], Nov 7, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11613)
      - ITP Culinary Arts Group Shot [Total negs: 11], Nov 15, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11614)
      - Pensioner Aids Luncheon Group Photo [Total negs: 11], Nov 16, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11615)
      - Annual Childrens Party [Total negs: 52], Dec 2, 1995 (Box 9, Item 11616)
    - Sub-subseries I:N:2: HERE, Local 15 (Bartenders).
      - Frank Kenny [?] Local 15 Democratic Party Meeting [Total negs: 17], May 17, 1905 (Box 8, Item 11559)
      - Bartenders Nat. [?] Shubert [?] Dinner [Total negs: 40], Aug 5, 1964 (Box 8, Item 11556)
      - Webster Hall Kennedy and Wagner [?] [Total negs: 110], Sep 20, 1964 (Box 8, Item 11557)
      - Latin Quarter [Total negs: 63], Nov 23, 1964 (Box 8, Item 11558)
      - 30 East 29th Street School Photo [Total negs: 11], Feb 4, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11560)
      - School Graduation [Total negs: 38], Mar 11, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11561)
      - Leone's [?] Restaurant [Total negs: 33], Apr 10, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11562)
      - Scholarship Students Webster Hall [Total negs: 4], Jun 6, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11563)
      - Scholarship Students webster Hall [separated from 35 mm] [Total negs: 12], Jun 6, 1965 (Box 19, Item 11565)
      - Nat. [?] Schubert [?] Annual Dinner Throgs [?] Nert [?] Stadium [Total negs: 15], Jun 28, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11564)
      - Mayor Wagner Swearing in City Hall [Total negs: 44], Nov 22, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11566)
      - Latin Quarter [Total negs: 36], Nov 22, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11567)
      - Webster Hall Installation [Total negs: 18], Dec 12, 1965 (Box 8, Item 11568)
      - Sullivan Picket Line [Total negs: 16], Mar 16, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11569)
      - Scholarship Awards Webster Hall [Total negs: 15], Jun 12, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11570)
      - Merger with Local 29 Savoy Hall [Total negs: 31], Sep 15, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11571)
      - Governer Rockefeller 22 W 55th street [Total negs: 31], Oct 24, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11572)
      - Latin Quarter Harry Doshe [?] [Total negs: 63], Nov 19, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11573)
      - Membership Meeting Webster Hall [Total negs: 24], Dec 11, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11574)
      - Sunrise Village Bellmore, L. I. [Total negs: 36], Jan 13, 1967 (Box 8, Item 11575)
      - Lou Beirnstein Photo for Booklets Portraits [Total negs: 20], Apr 28, 1967 (Box 8, Item 11576)
      - Portraits [Total negs: 113], May 16, 1967 (Box 8, Item 11577)
      - Policy Meeting Geogr [?] House [Total negs: 42], Jun 5, 1967 (Box 8, Item 11578)
      - Webster Hall Student Scholarship [Total negs: 49], Jun 20, 1967 (Box 9, Item 11619)
      - Latin Quarter [Total negs: 35], Nov 20, 1967 (Box 8, Item 11579)
    - Sub-subseries I:N:3: HERE, Local 302 (Cafeteria Employees).
      - 25th Anniversary Hotel Diplomat [Total negs: 66], Feb 4, 1964 (Box 8, Item 11583)
      - Hotel Diplomat Horn & Hardart [Total negs: 32], Jan 24, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11584)
      - Hotel Diplomat H & H Meeting [Total negs: 40], Mar 10, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11585)
      - H & H Dance Diplomat Hotel [Total negs: 54], Mar 20, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11586)
      - H & H Contract Signing Committee Catherwood [?] [Total negs: 35], Mar 20, 1966 (Box 8, Item 11587)
      - Hotel Diplomat R[?] [Total negs: 76], Feb 16, 1967 (Box 9, Item 11621)
      - Installation Meeting Hotel Diplomat [Total negs: 55], Mar 21, 1967 (Box 9, Item 11622)
      - Class Photos [Total negs: 6], Jun 23, 1967 (Box 8, Item 11588)
      - Plaque Presentation [Total negs: 4], May 23, 1968 (Box 8, Item 11589)
      - Dinner D [?] Joe Fox Commidore Hotel [Total negs: 62], Jun 15, 1968 (Box 8, Item 11590)
      - General Membership Walter Corran [?] Retirement [Total negs: 47], May 30, 1974 (Box 8, Item 11591)
  - Subseries I:O: International Airline Pilots Association.
    - Kamber Group "Airline Pilots Demonstration" [sep. frm. Color] [Total negs: 121], Apr 24, 1989 (Box 15, Item 11835)
    - Kamber Group "Airline Pilots Demonstration" [sep. frm. B/w] [Total negs: 68], Apr 24, 1989 (Box 15, Item 11836)
  - Subseries I:P: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Local 220.
    - Installation Meeting Sun Luck Rest[aurant] [Total negs: 34], Dec 3, 1969 (Box 2, Item 8890)
    - Portraits and Groups [Total negs: 63], Feb 25, 1974 (Box 2, Item 8891)
    - Office Photos [Total negs: 22], Aug 28, 1974 (Box 2, Item 8892)
    - Meetings Sun Luck Rest[aurant?] [Total negs: 70], Nov 12, 1974 (Box 2, Item 8893)
  - Subseries I:Q: International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Local 12.
    - Ribbon Cutting & Dinner [Total negs: 122], Nov 3, 1994 (Box 12, Item 11706)
  - Subseries I:R: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Local 627.
    - Morris Horn Bayside Jewish Center [Total negs: 12], May 29, 1967 (Box 15, Item 11838)
    - "Weekend Seminar at Raleigh Hotel" [Total negs: 150], Sep 8, 1978 (Box 15, Item 11839)
    - "Myotobia [?] Foundation" honors Morris Horn & Murray [Total negs: 87], Jun 21, 1979 (Box 15, Item 11840)
    - Groups -- Portraits [Total negs: 72], Aug 18, 1980 (Box 15, Item 11841)
  - Subseries I:S: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3.
    - Union Art Class (print #34) [Total negs: 3], Nov 21, 1973 (Box 8, Item 11205)
    - Bay Berry, Roy Truelove B x W neg's From color slides [Total negs: 35], Jan 3, 1983 (Box 15, Item 11842)
    - Communion Breakfast Sheraton Center [Total negs: 96], Jan 9, 1983 (Box 15, Item 11843)
    - H. & S. and Bond Redemption [Total negs: 62], Jan 10, 1983 (Box 15, Item 11844)
    - Portrait Joe D'Angelo [Total negs: 20], Jan 11, 1983 (Box 15, Item 11845)
    - Brdwy. Maintenance Splicing [Total negs: 42], Jan 17, 1983 (Box 15, Item 11846)
    - Allied Club Installation [Total negs: 33], Feb 2, 1983 (Box 15, Item 11847)
    - Catholic Council [of Electrical Workers] Ladies Nite -- dinner dance [Total negs: 172], Feb 4, 1983 (Box 15, Item 11848)
    - Contract Signing [Total negs: 16], Feb 8, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11849)
    - Pension Meeting [Total negs: 123], Mar 10, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11850)
    - Pensioners Luncheon [Total negs: 25], Mar 10, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11852)
    - Electchester Cooperative house [Total negs: 91], Mar 11, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11853)
    - Welfare Club [Total negs: 203], Mar 12, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11854)
    - Allied Club St. Pattys Dinner [Total negs: 207], Mar 13, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11855)
    - Due [?] Process, 2 Rolls B x W, 2 Set of Contracts, Tom Caufield [Total negs: 70], Mar 14, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11856)
    - Apprentice Dinner [Total negs: 58], Mar 18, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11857)
    - Scholarship Awards [Total negs: 374], Mar 26, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11968)
    - Apprentice Exams [Total negs: 43], Apr 9, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11858)
    - Drug Abuse [Total negs: 56], Apr 10, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11851)
    - Queens Symphony Orchestra and Child. [Children?] [Total negs: 51], Apr 12, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11859)
    - Presentation Board Meeting [Total negs: 33], Apr 13, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11860)
    - Portraits Robert Reede [?] Bill Blaine [Total negs: 21], Apr 13, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11861)
    - Nomination of Officers [Total negs: 35], Apr 14, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11862)
    - Retirement Party at: Rambusch [Total negs: 5], Apr 29, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11863)
    - Catholic Council [of Electrical Workers] Communion Mass [Total negs: 134], May 1, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11864)
    - Apprentice Meeting Auditorium [Total negs: 41], May 5, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11934)
    - DMB Award to Dennis McCartney [Total negs: 39], May 17, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11935)
    - Greek Orthodox Council Communion Luncheon Reception House [Total negs: 48], May 22, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11936)
    - Elect. Square Club [Total negs: 154], Jun 3, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11937)
    - N. Y. School of Fashion A--Contract Ratification [Total negs: 121], Jun 9, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11938)
    - Retirees Luncheon [Total negs: 51], Jun 22, 1983 (Box 16, Item 11939)
    - 50-60 Year Members [Total negs: 138], Jun 27, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11940)
    - Negotiation Contract Meeting [Total negs: 33], Jun 30, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11941)
    - EFCOR [Total negs: 64], Aug 2, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11942)
    - Kut [?] .off[?] Meeting Labor Day Parade [Total negs: 65], Aug 3, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11943)
    - Weksler Instruments [Total negs: 51], Aug 11, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11944)
    - March on Washington Press Conference [Total negs: 39], Aug 12, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11945)
    - at Winston Network [Total negs: 21], Aug 17, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11946)
    - Portrait Bill Gillen [Total negs: 10], Aug 22, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11947)
    - W N Employees [Total negs: 45], Aug 22, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11948)
    - Bayberry [DMB Apprentice Seminar Ladies Class Retirees 5/83] [Prevailing Wage Council 5/13-15/83] [Square Club Bayberry Jul. 11/12 1983] [Supply Division Seminar 7/23-24/83] [Total negs: 160], Aug 24, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11949)
    - Press Conference [Total negs: 26], Aug 25, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11950)
    - Dail-A-Light Retirement Party [Total negs: 1], Aug 30, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11951)
    - "A" Meeting [Total negs: 26], Sep 8, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11952)
    - Copy Neg. Cris [?] Plunkett [Total negs: 9], Sep 8, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11953)
    - Westchester Mechanics [Total negs: 35], Sep 10, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11954)
    - David Rockefeller [Total negs: 20], Sep 14, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11955)
    - TWU Building "Gov. Cuomo Breakfast" [Total negs: 55], Sep 16, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11956)
    - DMB Division [Total negs: 30], Sep 20, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11957)
    - Cable Splicing Class [Total negs: 46], Sep 26, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11958)
    - Colombus Party [Total negs: 108], Oct 2, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11959)
    - Joint Industry Bd., Develop & Process Bayberry [Empire State college seminar] [Total negs: 62], Oct 3, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11960)
    - Welfare Club [Total negs: 35], Oct 4, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11961)
    - Supply [Total negs: 37], Oct 4, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11969)
    - "Pioneer Club Luncheon" [Total negs: 53], Oct 11, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11962)
    - ABM Estimating Course [Total negs: 33], Oct 12, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11963)
    - Develop $ Contact [?] AFL-CIO Florida Convention [?] [Total negs: 9], Oct 15, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11964)
    - "Political Action Meeting" [Total negs: 106], Oct 15, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11965)
    - Bronx Theaters Employees at Work [Total negs: 27], Oct 18, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11966)
    - Allied Club dinner-dance [Total negs: 167], Oct 21, 1983 (Box 17, Item 11967)
    - M-Test, A-Test [Total negs: 34], Oct 22, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11970)
    - Greek Council annual dinner [Total negs: 71], Oct 22, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11971)
    - Welfare Club -Breakfast [Total negs: 130], Oct 23, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11972)
    - Out of Town Meeting [Total negs: 104], Oct 27, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11973)
    - Halloween Party [Total negs: 63], Oct 30, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11974)
    - Pension Reunion [?] Waldorf Astoria [Total negs: 114], Nov 4, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11975)
    - D..[?] & G..[?] Jerry Sullivan [Total negs: 42], Nov 9, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11976)
    - Latimer [?] Club [Total negs: 99], Nov 12, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11977)
    - Electchester A. A. awards [Total negs: 116], Nov 13, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11978)
    - DBM Meeting [Total negs: 62], Nov 15, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11979)
    - M. T. A. Demonstration [Total negs: 30], Nov 18, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11980)
    - Annuity Dinner [Total negs: 89], Dec 8, 1983 (Box 18, Item 11982)
    - Mike Gordenfeld [?] Shea Stadium [Total negs: 32], Nov 1983 (Box 18, Item 11981)
  - Subseries I:T: International Ladies' Garment Workers Union.
    - Local 32 Arts and Crafts (print #12) [Total negs: 3], May 23, 1905 (Box 8, Item 11212)
    - Wash.DC Jobs, Rally [Total negs: 9], Apr 26, 1975 (Box 175, Item 11202)
  - Subseries I:U: International Machinists Union.
    - NBC-GE Building NYC -- CLC Rally [Total negs: 111], Jun 27, 1997 (Box 15, Item 11837)
  - Subseries I:V: International Printing and Graphic Communications Union, Local 51.
    - Unemployment Checks [Total negs: 12], Sep 15, 1971 (Box 14, Item 11819)
    - North American Conference I..[?] M..[?] Westbury, N. Y. [Total negs: 126], Aug 11, 1973 (Box 14, Item 11820)
    - 40 & 50 Year Membership "presenting pins" [Total negs: 49], May 17, 1981 (Box 14, Item 11821)
    - N. Y. C. Swearing in of Officer [Total negs: 46], Apr 28, 1982 (Box 14, Item 11822)
    - Awards [Total negs: 16], May 15, 1983 (Box 14, Item 11823)
    - Scholarship Awards [Total negs: 53], Jun 1, 1983 (Box 14, Item 11824)
    - Local 51 [Total negs: 20], Jun 5, 1984 (Box 14, Item 11825)
    - "New Offices Grand Opening" [Total negs: 121], Jun 12, 1984 (Box 14, Item 11826)
    - Pension Meeting [Total negs: 33], Sep 23, 1984 (Box 14, Item 11827)
    - Installation of Officers [Total negs: 110], Apr 24, 1985 (Box 14, Item 11828)
    - "Pin Presentation" [Total negs: 44], Sep 22, 1985 (Box 15, Item 11829)
    - Local 51 [Total negs: 28], Sep 21, 1986 (Box 15, Item 11830)
    - Union Meeting [Total negs: 21], Sep 13, 1987 (Box 15, Item 11831)
    - Installation [Total negs: 8], Apr 27, 1988 (Box 15, Item 11832)
    - 40-50 yr. Pins [Total negs: 15], Sep 18, 1988 (Box 15, Item 11833)
    - "Pins" [Total negs: 34], Sep 17, 1989 (Box 15, Item 11834)
  - Subseries I:W: Textile Workers Union of America.
    - Poor People's March, Washington, D.C. [Total negs: 3], Jun 19, 1968 (Box 8, Item 11203)
    - Oneita State [Total negs: 3], Jun 28, 1973 (Box 8, Item 11204)
  - Subseries I:X: United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 342,.
    - Contract neg. Meetings [separated from 35mm] [Total negs: 18], undated (Box 10, Item 11655)
    - Petition Signing Staten Island Dougleston, Long Island [Total negs: 24], undated (Box 11, Item 11684)
    - Brooklyn Office Political Action Meeting [Total negs: 15], undated (Box 11, Item 11685)
    - Shop Stewards Meeting International. - Huntington 1/8/1967 [separated from 35mm] [Total negs: 16], Jan 8, 1967 (Box 10, Item 11654)
    - Membership Meeting International - Huntington [sep. from 35 mm] [Total negs: 3], Apr 10, 1967 (Box 10, Item 11656)
    - Women's Committee Cornell [Total negs: 20], Jun 3, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11623)
    - Photo Story ($PL) [?] Apprentice School [Total negs: 11], Jun 9, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11624)
    - Wedgewood Theater Women Committee [Total negs: 9], Jun 12, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11625)
    - Safety Program Apprentice School [Total negs: 38], Jun 12, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11626)
    - Women's Committee Cornell for L. I. Press [Total negs: 24], Jun 17, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11627)
    - Safety Management Jamaica [Total negs: 23], Jun 18, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11628)
    - Memorial Services for Ben Levine Americana [Total negs: 103], Jun 22, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11629)
    - Champion Softball Game Herricks, L. I. [Total negs: 24], Jun 28, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11630)
    - Apprentice School Graduation [Total negs: 32], Jul 25, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11631)
    - Softball Trophys [Total negs: 16], Jul 28, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11632)
    - Women's Bowling Staten Island [Total negs: 26], Sep 2, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11633)
    - Membership Meetings Huntington and In it [?] [Total negs: 32], Sep 7, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11634)
    - Cornell Communication Session [Total negs: 12], Sep 9, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11635)
    - Women Committee Dinner Dance Hampton Bay (Canal Place Inn) [Total negs: 68], Sep 27, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11636)
    - Apprentice School Visitors from Turkey 10AM [Total negs: 24], Sep 29, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11637)
    - Cope Endorsement Huntington [Total negs: 21], Sep 29, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11638)
    - A & P Part Time Wage Adjustments Staten Island [Total negs: 15], Oct 5, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11639)
    - Shop Steward Meeting, Jamaica and Huntington [Total negs: 46], Oct 13, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11640)
    - Women's Division Dinner Dance Micali Heroes Bay Ridge Brooklyn [Total negs: 43], Oct 19, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11641)
    - Apprentice School Photos off T. V. Screen WPIX - Channel 11 [Total negs: 17], Oct 22, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11642)
    - Cope [?] Jamaica, Judge Scalone Borough President Sidney Levine [?] [Total negs: 17], Oct 27, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11643)
    - Women's Committee Jamaica [?] [Total negs: 18], Oct 28, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11644)
    - Cage [?] Drawing Jamaica [Total negs: 24], Oct 29, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11645)
    - Contract Membership Meeting MIT [?] Republic Lodge [Total negs: 85], Nov 10, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11646)
    - Safety Seminar Meeting Jamaica [Total negs: 36], Nov 18, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11647)
    - Bowling - Women New Blouses [?] Staten Island [Total negs: 15], Nov 18, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11648)
    - Apprentice School Huntington Senior Citizens [Total negs: 18], Nov 19, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11649)
    - Independent Contract Negotiations MIT Hotel [Total negs: 35], Nov 19, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11650)
    - Cope [?] Winners Staten Island [Total negs: 7], Nov 24, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11651)
    - Apprentice School Graduation [Total negs: 29], Nov 29, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11652)
    - Executive Board & Negotiation Committee council Training [Total negs: 27], Dec 1, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11653)
    - Orphan Party Jamaica [Total negs: 22], Dec 7, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11657)
    - Orphan Christmas Party Brooklyn Office [Total negs: 22], Dec 10, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11658)
    - G. E. Demonstration Huntington Walt Whitman Shopping Center [Total negs: 79], Dec 13, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11659)
    - Atlantic Service Pickets [Total negs: 15], Dec 15, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11660)
    - Orphan Christmas Party Huntington [Total negs: 31], Dec 16, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11661)
    - Orphans Christmas Party Staten Island [Total negs: 18], Dec 21, 1969 (Box 10, Item 11662)
    - Independent Contract Meeting MIT Hotel [Total negs: 26], Jan 18, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11663)
    - Independent Contract Meeting Init. [?] Hotel and Patchogue, Long Island [Total negs: 52], Jan 25, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11664)
    - Ballet Mailing [Total negs: 17], Jan 28, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11665)
    - JOWA Beef at A & P Roosevelt Ave & 50th Street [Total negs: 36], Jan 31, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11666)
    - Ballot Committee Jamaica [Total negs: 39], Feb 5, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11667)
    - Blood Bank Brooklyn, New York [Total negs: 342], Mar 2, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11668)
    - Consumer Affairs Senior Lazarus Brooklyn Office [Total negs: 24], Mar 9, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11669)
    - Pre-Retirement Jamaica [Total negs: 20], Mar 25, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11670)
    - Consumer Affairs Jamaica [Total negs: 26], Apr 6, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11671)
    - Joint [?] Industry Safety [Total negs: 20], Apr 8, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11672)
    - Softball Hermits [?] Field [Total negs: 32], Apr 19, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11673)